<LATEST_RELEASE>1.6.1.1</LATEST_RELEASE>
<RELEASE_LINK>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oHg5SJYRHA0</RELEASE_LINK>
<Log>
  
Yay! New big update to the MixUp App!
Watch our video about this update and try out the new features for your business.

- MixUp is now fully compatible with Spinner360 platforms and works with GoPro (10,11,12) Black cameras!
   Especially for working with 360 booths we have created a new mode of operation - Admin Mode.
   This is a super convenient and beautiful control interface for the booth administrator at the event.
  
- With the help of hotkeys you can control the platform rotation and shooting remotely. 
   We also made a special lock mode so that guests can't unauthorizedly start shooting or change your settings.
   In Admin mode we've built in the gallery, all you need is one Surface tablet to work with the 360 booth.

- For Gopro cameras we've made a helpful assistant for connecting to your camera via WiFi.
   You can also work with GoPro via USB and use it simply as a SlowMo camera in the booth.
  
- To make SlowMo work well, we've added speed settings for your videos, which further enhances the capabilities of the video editor. 
   You can speed up and slow down any video regardless of its FPS.
   It's never been so convenient to customize your cool video presets for 360 booth. 
   We have also added the ability to work with SlowMo video for Canon cameras.

- For Canon cameras, you can now set custom Live View exposure settings. 
   This is useful for working with flash or in difficult lighting conditions.

- The menus now have on-screen keyboard support, when you interact with a text field it will automatically open (if enabled in Preferences)

- For projects you can now add a custom preview for photo mode. 
   This is very handy if you are working with chromakey and just want to show what the background of the photo will be. 
   If the custom photo preview is not loaded, the preview will be generated automatically.

And many more small updates, improvements and fixes.
</Log>
